Finding aid to the Classes of 1981-1990 records CA.MS.01027
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1981-1990 records
1977-2006
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1981.
CA.MS.01027
19.0 linear feet (35 containers)
College Archives has been collecting class material dating back to the Class of 1879. The Classes of 1981-1990 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1981-1990 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Biographical / Historical
College Archives has been collecting class material dating back to the Class of 1879. Classes of 1981-1990 records combine the student material from those graduating classes into one record group.
Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College -- Students; Smith College. Class of 1982.; Smith College. Class of 1983.; Smith College. Class of 1984.; Smith College. Class of 1985.; Smith College. Class of 1986.; Smith College. Class of 1987.; Smith College. Class of 1988.; Smith College. Class of 1989.; Smith College. Class of 1990.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College--Students.
- Class of 1981 Records, 1977-2006; 0.833 linear feet (2 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1981 was the 103rd graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1981 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1981, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - General, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Concert, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1977-1978 (Box 2279, Folder 4)
  - Groups, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 5)
  - Ivy Day, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 7)
  - Class Letters, 1982; 2002 (Box 2279, Folder 8)
  - Reunion, 2001 (Box 2279, Folder 9)
  - Reunion, 2006 (Box 2279, Folder 10)
  - Who's Who, 1977 (Box 2279, Folder 11)
  - Yearbook, 1981 (Box 2279, Folder 12)
  - Hershey, Joan - letters, 1977-1981 (Box 2279.1)
- Class of 1982 Records, 1978-1992; 1.25 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1982 was the 104th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1982 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1982, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1978-1982 (Box 2280, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1978-1979 (Box 2280, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 5)
  - Last Chapel, 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 6)
  - New Faces, 1978-1979 (Box 2280, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1982 (Box 2280, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2280, Folder 9)
  - Super Sundae Sunday, 1979 (Box 2280, Folder 10)
  - Yearbook (Box 2281)
    - General, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 1)
    - A, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 2)
    - Bab-Bat, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 3)
    - Bla-Bou, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 4)
    - Bra-Byn, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 5)
    - Caf-Cla, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 6)
    - Cle-Cur, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 7)
    - Dah-Dic, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 8)
    - Dig-Dw, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 9)
    - E, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 10)
    - Fa-Fl, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 11)
    - Fo-Fu, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 12)
    - Ga-Gi, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 13)
    - Gl-Gu, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 14)
    - Ha-Hen, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 15)
    - Hes-Ho, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 16)
    - I, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 17)
    - J, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 18)
    - Ka-Kel, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 19)
    - Ken-Kur, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 20)
    - La-Lef, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 21)
    - Len-Lu, 1982 (Box 2281, Folder 22)
    - Ma-May, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 1)
    - Mc-Me, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 2)
    - Mf-My, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 3)
    - N, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 4)
    - O, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 5)
    - Pa-Pe, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 6)
    - Ph, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 7)
    - Po-Pu, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 8)
    - Q, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 9)
    - Ra-Ri, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 10)
    - Ro-Ru, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 11)
    - Sa-Sh, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 12)
    - Si-Sp, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 13)
    - Sr-Sv, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 14)
    - T, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 15)
    - U, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 16)
    - V, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 17)
    - Wa-We, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 18)
    - Wh-Wu, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 19)
    - Y, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 20)
    - Z, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 21)
  - Candids, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 22)
  - Christmas Season, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 23)
  - Clubs-A-Ph, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 24)
  - Clubs-Pr-Wr, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 25)
  - Educational, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 26)
  - Faculty, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 27)
  - Houses, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 28)
  - Houses and Buildings, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 29)
  - Living, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 30)
  - Not Used, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 31)
  - Rally Day, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 32)
  - Senators, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 33)
  - Sports, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 34)
  - Student Activities, 1982 (Box 2282, Folder 35)
- Class of 1983 Records, 1979-2003; 2.667 linear feet (6 containers)
  The Class of 1983 was the 105th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1983 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1983, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1979-1980 (Box 2283, Folder 3)
  - Ivy Day, 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 4)
  - Last Chapel, 1983 (Box 2283, Folder 5)
  - Class Letters, 1983-2003 (Box 2283, Folder 6)
  - New Faces, 1979-1980 (Box 2283, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Box 2283, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1993 (Box 2283, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1998 (Box 2283, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 2003 (Box 2283, Folder 11)
  - Individuals L-Z (Box 2284)
  - Sophomore Year Scrapbook Contents, 1980-1981 (Box 2285)
  - Yearbook Photographs (Box 2286)
    - A, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 1)
    - B-Bl, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 2)
    - Bi-Bo, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 3)
    - Bo-Bz, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 4)
    - C-Ci, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 5)
    - Cl-Coh, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 6)
    - Coll-Cu, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 7)
    - D, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 8)
    - E, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 9)
    - F-Fi, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 10)
    - Fo-Fu, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 11)
    - Ga-Gi, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 12)
    - Go-Gu, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 13)
    - Ha, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 14)
    - He-Hu, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 15)
    - I-J, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 16)
    - Ka-Ke, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 17)
    - Kh-Ky, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 18)
    - L, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 19)
    - Ma-Me, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 20)
    - Mi-Mu, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 21)
    - N, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 22)
    - O, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 23)
    - Pa-Pe, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 24)
    - Pi-Pu, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 25)
    - R, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 26)
    - Sa-Se, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 27)
    - Sq-Sm, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 28)
    - Sn-Sw, 1983 (Box 2286, Folder 29)
    - Ta-To, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 1)
    - Tr-Tu, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 2)
    - U-V, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 3)
    - W-Wh, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 4)
    - Wi-Wr, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 5)
    - Y, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 6)
    - Z, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 7)
  - Academic Scenes, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 8)
  - Athletics, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 9)
  - Davis Center Scenes, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 10)
  - Editing Materials, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 11)
  - Events-Outdoor, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Groups, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 13)
  - House Activities, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 14)
  - House Groups A-D, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 15)
  - House Groups E-H, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 16)
  - House Groups I-O, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 17)
  - House Groups P-Z, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 18)
  - Outdoor Scenes, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 20)
  - Sports, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 21)
  - Not Used, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 22)
  - Students Outdoors, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 23)
  - Student Clubs, 1983 (Box 2287, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbooks, 1980-1981, 1982-1983 (Box 2287.1)
- Class of 1984 Records, 1980-1999; 0.417 linear feet (1 container)
  The Class of 1984 was the 106th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1984 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1984, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1980 (Box 2288, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1984 (Box 2288, Folder 2)
  - Ivy Day, 1984 (Box 2288, Folder 3)
  - Last Chapel, 1984 (Box 2288, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2288, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1989 (Box 2288, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2288, Folder 7)
- Class of 1985 Records, 1981-2005; 2.5 linear feet (4 containers)
  The Class of 1985 was the 107th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1985 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1985, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - General, 1981 (Box 2289, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1985 (Box 2289, Folder 2)
  - Ivy Day, 1985 (Box 2289, Folder 3)
  - Reunion, 1990 (Box 2289, Folder 4)
  - Reunion, 1995 (Box 2289, Folder 5)
  - Reunion, 2000 (Box 2289, Folder 6)
  - Reunion, 2005 (Box 2289, Folder 7)
  - Yearbook Photographs (Box 2290)
    - Candids, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 1)
    - Candids, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 2)
    - Candids, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 3)
    - Faculty, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 4)
    - Organizations, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 5)
    - Senior Photographs
      - A, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 6)
      - B, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 7)
      - C, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 8)
      - D, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 9)
      - E, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 10)
      - F, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 11)
      - G, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 12)
      - H, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 13)
      - I, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 14)
      - J, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 15)
      - K, 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 16)
      - L, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 1)
      - M, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 2)
      - N, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 3)
      - O, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 4)
      - P-Q, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 5)
      - R, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 6)
      - S, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 7)
      - T, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 8)
      - U-V, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 9)
      - W, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 10)
      - Y-Z, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 12)
  - Photographs Not Used, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 13)
  - Rotner Proofs, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 14)
  - Contact Sheets, 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbooks - freshman, sophomore, and senior years, 1982-1991 (Box 2291.1)
- Class of 1986 Records, 1982-2005; 2.208 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1986 was the 108th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1986 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1986, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  The Class of 1986 Records boxes also contain the Individual biographical files, not listed here. They often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - Commencement, 1986 (Box 2292, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1986 (Box 2292, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1982 (Box 2292, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1982-1986 (Box 2292, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1986 (Box 2292, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1985 (Box 2292, Folder 6)
  - Sophomore Push, 1984 (Box 2292, Folder 7)
  - Class Letters, 2003 (Box 2292, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1996-2005 (Box 2292, Folder 9)
  - Yearbook Photographs, 1986 (Box 2293, Folder 1)
  - Yearbook Photographs, 1986 (Box 2293, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook - junior year, 1984-1985 (Box 2293.1)
- Class of 1987 Records, 1983-1998; 1.625 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1987 was the 109th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1987 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1987, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1987 (Box 2294, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1987 (Box 2294, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Record, 1983 (Box 2294, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1983-1987 (Box 2294, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1987 (Box 2294, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1986 (Box 2294, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1987 (Box 2294, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 1998 (Box 2294, Folder 8)
  - Orientation, 1983 (Box 2294, Folder 9)
  - Sophomore Push, 1985 (Box 2294, Folder 10)
  - Senior Photographs (Box 2295)
    - A, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 1)
    - B, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 2)
    - C, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 3)
    - D, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 4)
    - E-F, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 5)
    - G, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 6)
    - H, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 7)
    - I-K, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 8)
    - L, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 9)
    - M, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 10)
    - N-O, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 11)
    - P-Q, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 12)
    - R, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 13)
    - S, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 14)
    - T, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 15)
    - V-Z, 1986 (Box 2295, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 2295.1)
- Class of 1988 Records, 1984-2005; 1.458 linear feet (4 containers)
  The Class of 1988 was the 110th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1988 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1988, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Record, 1984-1985 (Box 2296, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1984-1988 (Box 2296, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1987 (Box 2296, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1988 (Box 2296, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter, 2005 (Box 2296, Folder 8)
  - Sophomore Push, 1986 (Box 2296, Folder 9)
  - 10th Reunion, 1998 (Box 2296, Folder 10)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 2296)
  - Individuals E-N (Box 2297)
  - Individuals O-Z (Box 2298)
  - Finn, Heather Anne Clare - class notes (Box 2299)
- Class of 1989 Records, 1985-2004; 3.0 linear feet (3 containers)
  The Class of 1989 was the 111th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1989 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1989, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Class Day, 1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 3)
  - Groups, 1985-1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 4)
  - Ivy Day, 1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 5)
  - Junior Ushers, 1988 (Box 2299.1, Folder 6)
  - Last Chapel, 1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 7)
  - Class Letters, 2002-2004 (Box 2299.1, Folder 8)
  - President's Masked Ball, 1989 (Box 2299.1, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1994 (Box 2299.1, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1999 (Box 2299.1, Folder 11)
  - Sophomore Push, 1987 (Box 2299.1, Folder 12)
  - Who's Who, 1985-1986 (Box 2299.1, Folder 13)
  - 5th Reunion scrapbook, 1994 (Box 2299.2)
  - Scrapbook, 1988-1989 (Box 2299.3)
- Class of 1990 Records, 1986-2005; 3.042 linear feet (6 containers)
  The Class of 1990 was the 112th graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1990 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1990, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Commencement, 1990 (Box 2300, Folder 1)
  - Groups, 1986-1990 (Box 2300, Folder 2)
  - Ivy Day, 1990 (Box 2300, Folder 3)
  - Junior Ushers, 1989 (Box 2300, Folder 4)
  - Last Chapel, 1990 (Box 2300, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1989-2001 (Box 2300, Folder 6)
  - Sophomore Push, 1988 (Box 2300, Folder 7)
  - Who's Who, 1986-1987 (Box 2300, Folder 8)
  - Yearbook Photographs, 1990 (Box 2300, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1992 (Box 2300.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 2000 (Box 2300.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 2000 (Box 2300.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 2000 (Box 2300.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 2005 (Box 2300.1, Folder 5)
  - Nichols, Elizabeth A. - research files for Paradise Lost and Regained Foreign Professors at Smith College (Box 2300.2)
  - Scrapbook, 1989-1990 (Box 2300.3)
  - Scrapbook - freshman year, 1986-1987 (Box 2300.4)
  - Scrapbook - sophomore year, 1987-1988 (Box 2300.5)